
{title: 'parrotsQuestion',
front: 'What is the proper name for a group of parrots?',
back: 'pandemonium'};
{title: 'earsQuestion',
front: 'What animal has the largest ears?',
back: 'African elephant'};
{title: 'alligatorQuestion',
front: 'In the US, where can alligators and crocodiles be found living together in the wild?',
back: 'South Florida'};
{title: 'lionQuestion',
front: 'What is the proper name for a group of lions?',
back: 'A pride'};
{title: 'snakeQuestion',
front: 'The longest snake ever held in captivty belongs to what species?',
back: 'python'};
{title: 'octopusQuestion',
front: 'How many hearts does an octopus have?',
back: 'three'};
{title: 'sleepyQuestion',
front: 'What is the sleepiest animal in the world, sleeping around 22 hours each day?',
back: 'Koala'};
{title: 'polarQuestion',
front: 'Polar bears feed mainly on what animal?',
back: 'seals'};
{title: 'pearlQuestion',
front: 'Natural pearls are found in what sea creature?',
back: 'Oyster'};
{title: 'fastestQuestion',
front: 'What is the fastest fish in the ocean?',
back: 'Sailfish'};
{title: 'legsQuestion',
front: 'Which animal has the most legs?',
back: 'Millipede'};